Guide to the Frauke Heard-Bey and David Heard collection AD.MC.064
NYU Abu Dhabi, Archives and Special Collections
- Government publications, 1968-2007
  - United Arab Emirates government: Official Gazette, and related (Arabic), 1971-1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 82, Year 10, August 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 83, Year 10 (two issues), September 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 84, Year 10 (two issues), October 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 85, Year 10, November 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 86, Year 10, December 1980
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 87, Year 11, January 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 88, Year 11, February 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 89, Year 11, March 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 90, Year 11, April 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 91, Year 11, May 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 92, Year 11, June 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 93, Year 11, July 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 94, Year 11, July 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 95, Year 11, September 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 96, Year 11, October 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 97, Year 11, November 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 98, Year 11, November 1981
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 99, Year 11, December 1999
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 233, Year 22, January 1992 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 234, Year 22, February 1992 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 235, Year 22, March 1992 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 236, Year 22, April 1992 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 237, Year 22, April 1992 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 238, Year 22, May 1992 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 239, Year 22, June 1992 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 240, Year 22, July 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 241, Year 22, August 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 242, Year 22, September 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 243, Year 22, October 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 244, Year 22, October 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 245, Year 22, November 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 246, Year 22, December 1992
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 247, Year 23, January 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 247, Year 23, Supplement (mukarar), February 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 248, Year 23, February 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 249, Year 23 (two copies), March 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 250, Year 23 (two copies), April 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 251, Year 23, May 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 252, Year 23, June 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 254, Year 23, August 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 255, Year 23, September 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 256, Year 23, September 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 258, Year 23 (two copies), October 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 259, Year 23 (two copies), November 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 260, Year 23 (two copies), December 1993
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 262, Year 24, February 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 263, Year 24, March 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 264, Year 24, April 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 265, Year 24, May 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 266, Year 24, June 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 267, Year 24, July 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 268, Year 24, August 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 269, Year 24, September 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 270, Year 24, October 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 271, Year 24, November 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 272, Year 24, November 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 273, Year 24, December 1994
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 274, Year 25, January 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 275, Year 25, February 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 276, Year 25, March 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 277, Year 25, April 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 279, Year 25, May 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 280, Year 25, June 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 282, Year 25, July 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 283, Year 25, August 1995
    - al-Jarīdah al-rasmīyah (Official Gazette). No. 284, Year 25, September 1995
  - United Arab Emirates government: Official Gazette (English translation), 1988-2007
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 18, Issue 194, Nov. 1988 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 19, Issues 196-201, January - June 1989 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 19, Issues 202-208, July - December 1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 20, Issues 210-214, February - June 1990 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 20, Issues 215-220, July - December 1990 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 21, Issues 222-226, February - June 1991 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 21, Issues 227-232, July - December 1991 (Box 22, Folder 1)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 22, Issues 233-238, January - May 1992 (Box 22, Folder 2)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 22, Issues 240-241, 244-246, July - August, October - Decembert 1992 (Box 22, Folder 3)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 23, Issues 247-252, January - May 1993 (Box 22, Folder 4)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 23, Issues 253-256, 259-260, July - September, November - December 1993 (Box 22, Folder 5)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 24, Issues 261-266, January - June 1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 24, Issues 267-273, July - December 1994 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 25, Issues 274-281, January - June 1995 (Box 22, Folder 7)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 25, Issues 282-288, July - December 1995 (Box 22, Folder 9)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 26, Issues 289-294, January - June 1996 (Box 22, Folder 10)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 26, Issues 295-300, July - December 1996 (Box 22, Folder 11)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 27, Issues 301-306, January - June 1997 (Box 22, Folder 12)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 27, Issues 307-312, July - December 1997 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 28, Issues 313-319, January - June 1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 28, Issues 320-325, 328, July - October, December 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 34, Issues 414-415, May - June 2004 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 34, Issues 416-423, July - December 2004 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 35, Issues 424-431, January - June 2005 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 35, Issues 432-441, July - December 2005 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 36, Issues 442-449, January - June 2006 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 36, Issues 451-452, 457, 459, July, November - December 2006 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - UAE. Official Gazette (English translation), Year 37, Issues 460-461, January 2007 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - UAE. Official Gazette. Penal Code and Restoration Code [Arabic], 1992
- Law, 1998-2007
  - Emirates Law: a newsletter of Fox and Gibbons and Co. and Habib Al Mulla and Co., Issue no. 18, March 1998 (Box 23, Folder 11)
  - Emirates Law Journal (Abu Dhabi, Dubai: Emirates Advocates), February 2004 (Box 23, Folder 12)
  - Law Update, Al Tamimi and Company Advocates, Issue no. 135, June 2002 (Box 23, Folder 13)
  - Law Update, Al Tamimi and Company Advocates, Issue no. 142, January 2003 (Box 23, Folder 14)
  - Law Update, Al Tamimi and Company Advocates, Issue no. 144, March 2003 (Box 23, Folder 15)
  - Law Update, Al Tamimi and Company Advocates, Issue no. 150, September 2003 (Box 23, Folder 16)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume I, Issue 1, January 1997 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume I, Issue 4, October 1997 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume II, Issue 1, January 1998 (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume II, Issue 2, April 1998 (Box 24, Folder 4)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume II, Issue 3, July 1998 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume II, Issue 4, October 1998 (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume III, Issue 1, January 1999 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume III, Issue 2, April 1999 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume III, Issue 3, July 1999 (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume III, Issue 4, October 1999 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume IV, Issue 1, January 2000 (Box 24, Folder 11)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume IV, Issue 2, April 2000 (Box 24, Folder 12)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume IV, Issue 3, July 2000 (Box 24, Folder 13)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume IV, Issue 4, October 2000 (Box 24, Folder 14)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume V, Issue 1, January 2001 (Box 24, Folder 15)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume V, Issue 2, April 2001 (Box 24, Folder 16)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume V!, Issue 1, January 2002 (Box 24, Folder 17)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VI, Issue 2, April 2002 (Box 24, Folder 18)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VI, Issue 3, July 2002 (Box 24, Folder 19)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VI, Issue 4, October 2002 (Box 24, Folder 20)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VII, Issue 2, April 2003 (Box 24, Folder 21)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VII, Issue 4, October 2003 (Box 24, Folder 22)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VIII, Issue 1, January 2004 (Box 24, Folder 23)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VIII, Issue 2, April 2004 (Box 24, Folder 24)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume VIII, Issue 3, July 2004 (Box 24, Folder 25)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume IX, Issue 1, January 2005 (Box 24, Folder 26)
  - Lex Arabiae: Legal News of the Gulf, Volume XI, Issue 4, January 2007 (Box 24, Folder 27)
  - Seminar: Legal Issues Related to Commercial Activities in the UAE and the Gulf: "Advantages Available Under Double Taxation Treaties with Focus on the Kingdom of Saudi Arabia and the United Arab Emirates," Udo Rosin and Ulrich Berdelmann, Intercontinental Hotel, Abu Dhabi, 15 March 1998 (Box 24, Folder 28)
  - Seminar: Legal Issues Related to Commercial Activities in the UAE and the Gulf: "Commercial Importance of Trademarks and Their Protection in the United Arab Emirates, Robert Gebhardt and Christoph Schmitt, Intercontinental Hotel, Abu Dhabi, 15 March 1998 (Box 24, Folder 29)
- Oil industry and energy sector, 1969-2007
  - Abu Dhabi Petroleum Company Limited. Review, 1969 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Abu Dhabi Petroleum Company Limited. 'Amalīyāt Sharikat Nefṭ Abū Ẓaby al-maḥdūdah [annual report], undated, circa 1971 (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 2, 5-12, May - December 1989 (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 14-24, January - June 1990 (Box 25, Folder 4)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 25-33, 35-36, July - December 1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 38, 40-41, 43-46, January - June 1991 (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 50-58, July - November 1991 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 63-64, 66-68, 70-72, February - June 1992 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 73-84, July - December 1992 (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 85-89, 91-96, January - June 1993 (Box 25, Folder 10)
  - ADCO: Al Waha; published by ADCO for its employees [Newsletter], Nos. 97-108, July - December 1993 (Box 25, Folder 11)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Annual Report, 1989 (Box 25, Folder 12)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Annual Report, 1992 (Box 25, Folder 13)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Annual Report, 1994 (Box 25, Folder 14)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations: Calendar, 1986 (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations: Calendar, 1993 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. ADCO Cares: Can You Afford Not To? (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Gifts of the Desert = Hibāt al-sạhṛāʼ, June 1982 (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations: Khaleej Times special report, "25th anniversary of first oil shipment", December 14, 1988 (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Who's Who: Management Team B, 1994 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - ADCO: Abu Dhabi Company for Onshore Oil Operations. Who's Who: Management Team B, 1996 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - ADGAS: Abu Dhabi Gas Liquefaction Co. Ltd. Two brochures, "ADGAS Expansion Inauguration" and ""Building for the 21st Century", 1994 (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - ADMA: Abu Dhabi Marine Areas Ltd. Annual Review of Operations, 1974 (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - ADMA: Abu Dhabi Marine Areas Ltd. Annual Review of Operations, 1976 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - ADMA: Abu Dhabi Marine Areas Ltd. [Prospectus in Japanese, describing offshore oil operations], 1973 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - ADMA-OPCO: Abu Dhabi Marine Operating Company (ADMA-OPCO). 15th Anniversary of Oil Exports, 1977 (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - ADMA-OPCO: Abu Dhabi Marine Operating Company (ADMA-OPCO). ADMA-OPCOs Annual Review of Operations, 1985 (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - ADMA-OPCO: Abu Dhabi Marine Operating Company (ADMA-OPCO). Annual Review, 1992 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - ADMA-OPCO: Abu Dhabi Marine Operating Company (ADMA-OPCO). ADMA-OPCO [Monthly Magazine], Vol. 21, Issue No. 258, July 2004 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News Special Issue - ADNOC, 1971-1991 (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, February 1992 (Box 26, Folder 17)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, March 1992 (Box 26, Folder 18)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, April 1992 (Box 26, Folder 19)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, May 1992 (Box 26, Folder 20)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, June 1992 (Box 26, Folder 21)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, July 1992 (Box 26, Folder 22)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, August 1992 (Box 26, Folder 23)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, September 1992 (Box 26, Folder 24)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, October 1992 (Box 26, Folder 25)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, November 1992 (Box 26, Folder 26)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, December 1992 (Box 26, Folder 27)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, January 1993 (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, March 1993 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, April 1993 (Box 27, Folder 3)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, May 1993 (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, June 1993 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, December 1994 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, February 1997 (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, June 2001 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, January 2003 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, February 2003 (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, March 2003 (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, April 2003 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, May 2003 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, September 2003 (Box 27, Folder 14)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, October 2003 (Box 27, Folder 15)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, November-December 2003 (Box 27, Folder 16)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, May-June, 2004 (Box 27, Folder 17)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, September-October 2004 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, November 2004 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, December 2004 (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, January 2005 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, February-March 2005 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, April-May 2005 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News (Special Supplement), May 2005 (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, August - September 2005 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, February-March 2006 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, April-June 2006 (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News [supplement, Petroleum Institute graduation], June 2006 (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, July-September, 2006 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, Issue 1, January - March 2007 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, 2nd issue, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, 3rd issue, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 12)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, 4th issue, 2007 (Box 28, Folder 13)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, 3rd issue, 2009 (Box 28, Folder 14)
  - ADNOC: ADNOC News, July 2011 (Box 28, Folder 15)
  - ADNOC. Annual Report, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - ADNOC. Annual Report, 1992 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - ADNOC: Abu Dhabi National Oil Company. 1971-1991 20 Years of Progress (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - ADNOC: Abu Dhabi National Oil Company. ADNOC People, July 2003 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - ADNOC: Abu Dhabi National Oil Company. Ruwais Housing Complex (RHC), undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - ADNOC: Abu Dhabi National Oil Company. Telephone Directory, January 1998 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Akhbār al-Batrūl wa al-Sinā'ah [Oil and Petroleum News, Issue 635, Year 21], February 1990 (Box 29, Folder 7)
  - Arab Oil & Gas Directory (Arab Petroleum Research Center), 1993 (Volume 76)
  - Arab Oil & Gas Directory (Arab Petroleum Research Center), 2001 (Volume 77)
  - Arab Oil & Gas Directory (Arab Petroleum Research Center), 2002 (Volume 78)
  - ARAMCO: Arabian American Oil Company. Translation Manual: Petroleum Technical Terms, 1973 (Box 29, Folder 8)
  - British Petroleum: What's the Alternative? BP Alternative Energy, undated, circa 1990s (Box 29, Folder 9)
  - Bunduq Company Limited: annual review of operations, 1977 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Energies: the International Magazine of Total, No. 37 [contains cover story on planned introduction of Euro currency, as well as feature on expedition to island of Socotra], Autumn 1998 (Box 29, Folder 11)
  - GASCO: Abu Dhabi Gas Industries Limited. Annual Report, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 12)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (46), March 2004 (Box 29, Folder 13)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (50), July-August 2004 (Box 29, Folder 14)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (51), January 2005 (Box 29, Folder 15)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (52), February 2005 (Box 29, Folder 16)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (54), April 2005 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - National Drilling Company: NDC News (55), May 2005 (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Oil & Gas Directory U.A.E., 1994 (Volume 79)
  - Oil & Gas Directory Arabian Gulf, 2001 (Volume 80)
  - Oil & Gas Directory Arabian Gulf, 2004 (Volume 81)
  - Petroleum Economist, Vol. XLI, No. 5, May 1974 (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Shell International Petroleum Company. Shell Briefing Service No.2: Oil Trading, 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Society of Petroleum Engineers. 1996 Society of Petroleum Engineers Membership Directory.
  - UAE: Ministry of Oil and Mineral Wealth: al-Bitrūl fī Dawlat al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttahịdah, 1974 (Volume 82)
  - UAE: Ministry of Oil and Mineral Wealth. Petroleum in the United Arab Emirates, 1974 (Volume 83)
  - UAE. Ministry of Petroleum and Mineral Resources. Statistics Department. UAE Oil Statistical Review, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Utaybah, Māniʻ Saʻīd. al-Batrūl wa-iqtiṣādīyāt al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah, 1977 (Volume 84)
    HD9576.U52 O8 1977a
  - Utaybah, Māniʻ Saʻīd: al-Batrūl wa-iqtiṣādīyāt al-Imārāt al-ʻArabīyah al-Muttaḥidah [2 volumes, slipcased], 1990 (Volume 85)
  - ZADCO: Zakum Development Company. A Closer Look at the Activities of ZADCO, October 1994 (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - ZADCO: Zakum Development Company. Profile, undated, circa 2007 (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - ZADCO. Oil and People: ZADCO, 1977-1992 (Volume 86)
    HD9576.U65 N34 1992
- Other GCC (Gulf Cooperation Council) countries, 1964-2011
  - General
    - al-Amānah al-ʻĀmmah lil-Marākiz wa-al-Hayʼāt al-ʻIlmīyah al-Muhtammah bi-Dirāsāt al-Khalīj al-ʻArabī wa-al-Jazīrah al-ʻArabīyah: al-anẓimah wa-al-ikhtiṣāṣāt wa-al-nashāṭāt (Baghdād: Manshūrāt Markaz Dirāsāt al-Khalīj al-ʻArabī bi-Jāmiʻat al-Baṣrah), 1979 (Volume 89)
      DS326.M29 1979
    - Cooperation Council for the Arab States of the Gulf. (London: ISC Ltd.), 1997 (Volume 87)
      HC415.3.A! C66 1997
    - The Cooperation Council for the Arab States of the Gulf, 1998 (Volume 88)
      HC415.3.A1 C66 1998
    - Cooperation Council for the Arab States of the Gulf. Business Briefing: GCC Region. World Markets Research Center, 1996 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Electricity Conservation and Sustainable Development in Arab GCC Countries. (Eschborn: Deutsche Gesellschaft fuer Technische Zusammenarbeit, GmbH, undated, circa 1998)
    - GCC Databook 1994. (Dubai: Drylands Consultants) (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - GCC Economic Databook. Robert Edwards (Motivate Publishing), 1996 (Volume 90)
      HC415.3 .G423 1996
    - GCC Population Databook. (Dubai: Drylands Consultants), 1995 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - "Growing Pains: the Gulf Co-operation Council countries: a survey. The Economist, 40 pages, February 8, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Gulf Co-operation, Achievements and Aspirations. (Bahrain: Gulf Public Relations Group), undated, circa 1985 (Volume 91)
      DS201 .G97